Woke up to rules that I never made,
Trapped in a life where dreams would fade.\⁠h
Counting the days in a hollow race,
Running so fast but stuck in place.
They say, "Just follow, don’t ask why,"
But I see the world and I wonder why—\⁠h
If living means to just obey,
Then when do I get my say?
Give me some air, give me some light,
Let me feel the world outside.\⁠h
One more chance, one more day,
Let me live in my own way.
I colored inside the lines they drew,
Hiding the shades of a life I knew.\⁠h
They called it wisdom, they called it fate,
But all I felt was a heavy weight.
They say, "Be perfect, don’t fall behind,"
But I’ve got a voice and I’ve got a mind.\⁠h
If life’s a song, then I won’t mime,
I’ll write my own, in my own time.
Give me some air, give me some light,
Let me feel the world outside.\⁠h
One more chance, one more day,
Let me live in my own way.
I don’t want regrets to hold me down,
No more fear, no more doubt.\⁠h
If I must fall, then let me fly,
At least I’ll know I tried.
Give me some air, give me some light,
Let me feel the world outside.\⁠h
One more chance, one more day,
Let me live in my own way.
Let me live before goodbye…