<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:32:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/webnovels/dear-kafka/ch-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:32:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/webnovels/dear-kafka/ch-0001/</guid>
      <description>Kyton The eyes were always there. Not real eyes, not reflections in a rain-slicked window or the passing glance of a stranger on the street. These were heavier. They pressed against the inside of his skull, a phantom weight behind his own gaze. Freedom? Freedom was a word for people who didn&amp;rsquo;t carry their own courtroom inside their head.&#xA;Kyton was a man who could disappear any day. No one would notice or care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Tao Teh Ching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/about-the-tao-teh-ching/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:15:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/about-the-tao-teh-ching/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve read around five different translations of the Tao Teh Ching. One particular one, I&amp;rsquo;ve read around twenty times. I think that it is quite a nice book. It states too many things that are quite relevant, but it&amp;rsquo;s so damn cryptic that half the time I feel that I&amp;rsquo;m the one making up the meanings in the book. Actually , now that I think about it , that might be the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Am I So Interested ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/why-am-i-so-interested-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 20:46:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/why-am-i-so-interested-/</guid>
      <description>I created this site initially to pretend that I am an arts student. But surprisingly enough, I am spending a whole lot of time trying to add more stuff to this site. And not just in terms of html. I am actually adding and planning more content.&#xA;After I was done writing the first story here , &amp;ldquo;The River That Carries The Sky&amp;rdquo; , I am already working on the next story &amp;ldquo;Dear Kafka&amp;rdquo;, not to mention the amount of songs I am generating and editing to put in here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Tracking People on the Web</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/on-tracking-people-on-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 02:57:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/on-tracking-people-on-the-web/</guid>
      <description>I like to write stories. But sometimes, I am curious as to how many people actually read them. So for a brief moment, I thought- &amp;ldquo;how about I find out how many people read my stories ?&amp;rdquo; But to do so, I had to create some js tracker on my site (maybe github provides one by default, I don&amp;rsquo;t know), but wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be stalking ? Why is it my business to know how many people visited my site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reason for Creating Another Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/the-reason-for-creating-another-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:23:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/the-reason-for-creating-another-blog/</guid>
      <description>Just to get this out of the picture. I already have another site&#xA;However, that one was meant to be a personal portfolio of sorts. But now I realize that I have no use of a personal portfolio. It&amp;rsquo;s not like I&amp;rsquo;m going to get a job anyway, so why bother with one. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ll live for long, so I decided to do whatever I liked until I died.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
