In this vast universe
Among the many stars\h
In a single vast blue planet\h
My small feelings of love would reach
to that tiny island where you are
Time had passed since I met you\h
And the letters adorning our\h
feelings are also increasing\h
Someday, they will echo unnoticed in our hearts
At times violently, at times sorrowfully
They will echo faraway, into the far-off distance
This tender song will change the world
Look now
The person who you cherish\h
Is right beside you
I wish\h
for this to reach just you
Resonate, my song of love\h
Look now...
Resound, my song of love
You come to realise,\h
that even when the two of\h
us should walk a dark road\h
The moon would illuminate our days
Never letting go of your hand I've clasped\h
Our feelings are strong
and we vow it's for all eternity\h
In the depths of eternity
I will surely say the exact same words\h
with my feelings still the same
But those words will never cease\h
they will turn into tears
Then to joy\h
Unable to speak
I'll just embrace you
Look now
The person who you cherish\h
Is right beside you
I wish\h
for this to reach just you
Resonate, my song of love\h
Look now...
Resound, my song of love
If it's a dream don't wake me up
If it's a dream don't wake me up\h
The time I've spent with you\h
Shall become a star
shining eternally
Look now
The person who you cherish\h
is right besides you
I wish\h
for this to reach just you
Oh resound, my song of love\h
Look now\h
the person who you cherish
Is right beside you\h
I wish
for this to reach just you\h
Resonate, my song of love
Look now...\h
Look now!
Resound, my song of love